<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Anterra Group Inc</title>
    <link>http://anterra.siteleaf.net</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2015 21:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>OMRI Approves Genesis AC02 </title>
      <link>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/omri-approves-genesis-ac02</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 22:39:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>Jeremy Ricketts</author>
      <guid>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/omri-approves-genesis-ac02</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AnTerra Group is pleased to announce that our new patent-pending pH control system &amp;ldquo;GENESIS AC02&amp;rdquo; has been approved to be used in certified organic production or food processing and handling according to the USDA National Organic Program Rule.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AnTerra Maintains Exclusive Ownerhip of Genesis AC02 Patent</title>
      <link>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/anterra-maintains-exclusive-ownerhip-of-genesis-ac02-patent</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2014 21:33:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Jeremy Ricketts</author>
      <guid>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/anterra-maintains-exclusive-ownerhip-of-genesis-ac02-patent</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AnTerra Group is pleased to announce that it has successfully resolved pending litigation in federal court in Orange County, which confirms AnTerra’s exclusive ownership of its U.S. Patent Number 8,420,143. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AnTerra’s patent, which issued in 2013, gives AnTerra all exclusive rights to license and use its innovative Genesis AC02 Organic Produce Wash System. The Genesis System utilizes carbon dioxide to optimize chlorine in fruit and vegetable wash systems, replacing conventional food grade acids such as citric acid with carbon dioxide, a safer, greener, and less costly approach to controlling pH in chlorine or surfactant based wash systems. The Genesis AC02 system has also shown improved microbiological control over conventional chlorine-based treatment systems.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genesis ACO2 Patent Issues</title>
      <link>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/genesis-aco2-patent-issues</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 19:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Jeremy Ricketts</author>
      <guid>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/genesis-aco2-patent-issues</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On April 16th, 2013, AnTerra Group, Inc. was issued Patent No# 8420143 for Genesis ACO2 , Organic Produce Wash System. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations to AnTerra Group on their development of a novel process method designed to utilize carbon dioxide to optimize chlorine in fruit and vegetable wash systems. The Genesis ACO2 System replaces conventional food grade acids such as citric with CO2 a safter, greener and less costly approach to control pH in chlorine or surfactant based wash systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/genesis&quot;&gt;Read more about the Genesis CO2 system&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AnTerra Makes Top Diversity Business List for 2009</title>
      <link>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/anterra-makes-top-diversity-business-list-for-2009</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 21:51:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Jeremy Ricketts</author>
      <guid>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/anterra-makes-top-diversity-business-list-for-2009</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Once again AnTerra is proud to announce that this year they have received two distinguishing awards from Diversity Business. &amp;ldquo;Top 100 Small Businesses in California&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Top 500 Small Businesses in the United States.&amp;rdquo; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This classification represents the top small businesses in the U.S., in sectors such as technology, manufacturing, food service and professional services. Large organizational buyers throughtout the country that do business with multicultural, small and women-owned businesses use the list. The winning companies will be honored at a special awards ceremony at Diversity Business&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;9 Annual Multicultural Business Conference&amp;rdquo;, taking place April 29th-May 1st, 2009 at the Disney’s Contemporary Resort in Orlando, Florida.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raw Material Prices Continue To Esclate</title>
      <link>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/raw-material-prices-continue-to-esclate</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2008 22:44:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Jeremy Ricketts</author>
      <guid>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/raw-material-prices-continue-to-esclate</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Raw material prices continue to rise. Sodium Hydroxide, Potassium Hydroxide, Citric Acid, Sulfuric Acid, Hydrochloric Acid, Phosphoric Acid and Propylene Glycol are just a few of the chemicals that are at all time highs with no end in sight.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Time Member of CCOF</title>
      <link>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/life-time-member-of-ccof</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 22:53:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Jeremy Ricketts</author>
      <guid>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/life-time-member-of-ccof</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Did you know that AnTerra Group, Inc. is a life time member of the California Certified Organic Farmers!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&quot;Diversity Business&quot; Awards Anterra Group, Inc.</title>
      <link>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/diversity-business-awards-anterra-group-inc</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2008 22:04:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Jeremy Ricketts</author>
      <guid>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/diversity-business-awards-anterra-group-inc</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Congratulations! AnTerra Group, Inc. is the recipient of the Diversity Business &amp;ldquo;Top 100 Women Owned Business In California&amp;rdquo; for 2007.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rising Prices for Sulfuric Acid</title>
      <link>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/rising-prices-for-sulfuric-acid</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 22:46:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Jeremy Ricketts</author>
      <guid>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/rising-prices-for-sulfuric-acid</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A recent article by Michael Mccoy, C&amp;amp;EN Northeast New Bureau, touches on the current events that are converging to drive up the price of sulfuric acid to record highs. He states that the spot price for sulfuric acid sold on the U.S. Gulf Coast is four times higher today than it was a year ago. Many manufacturing operations rely on this chemical and therefore have a widespread affect on many industrial users. Mccoy states that Robert Boyd, founder of the sulfur and sulfuric acid consulting firm PentaSul., believes that the prices will come down in the long term, but not before 2009&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For More information: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cen-online.org&quot;&gt;www.cen-online.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AnTerra Group Has Moved </title>
      <link>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/anterra-group-has-moved</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 22:54:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>Jeremy Ricketts</author>
      <guid>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/anterra-group-has-moved</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For those of you who might not know, AnTerra Group has moved to our new location as of June 1st, 2007. Please note our new address:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;25255 Cabot Road, Suite 215
Laguna Hills, CA 92653.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Phone and fax numbers are still the same.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See AnTerra Group at CCOF Conference</title>
      <link>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/see-anterra-group-at-ccof-conference</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2008 22:58:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <author>Jeremy Ricketts</author>
      <guid>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/see-anterra-group-at-ccof-conference</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The president of AnTerra Group, Inc. has been asked to be a guest speaker at the California Certified Organic Farmers Conference Jan. 22nd 23rd. He will be speeking on the importance of the proper use of cleaning and sanitation in the farming industry.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to AnTerra Shea Jones</title>
      <link>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/welcome-to-anterra-shea-jones</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2007 23:02:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <author>Jeremy Ricketts</author>
      <guid>http://anterra.siteleaf.net/news/welcome-to-anterra-shea-jones</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AnTerra Group would like to introduce and new associate member to our team! Shea Jones, will be managing our customer service department. Please don’t hesitate to contact her for all of your customer service needs. We are looking forward to having her as a part of AnTerra Group, Inc.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
